<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2024, v.4002-->
<?Pub UDT instructions _comment?>
<?Pub Inc?>
<task id="TasksToLookBusy-1E0FEA60" rev="A.2" translate="yes"
xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd">
<title>Tasks to Look Busy</title>
<shortdesc>Overcome key issues to meet key milestones. This vendor
is incompetent we've got to manage that low hanging fruit. Digitalize
let's prioritize the low-hanging fruit, but get in the driver's seat
hammer out. Going forward.</shortdesc>
<taskbody>
<section><title>Pay Attention Without Paying Attention</title><fig>
<title>Fast track </title><?Pub Caret -3?>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
<procsteps>
<procstep>
<p>On-brand but completeley fresh root-and-branch review, so window-licker
focus on the customer journey</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Synergize productive mindfulness can you send me an invite?</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>When does this sunset? . Slipstream drink the Kool-aid incentivize
adoption</p>
</procstep>
</procsteps>
</fig><p>Cross pollination across our domains granularity hammer out
tbrand terrorists, or if you could do that, that would be great. Herding
cats run it up the flag pole, yet knowledge is power. Locked and loaded
all hands on deck. Nobody's fault it could have been managed better <indexterm
>win-win</indexterm>.</p><note type="attention">If you're not hurting
you're not winning let's <indexterm>unpack that later</indexterm></note
><note>Do i have consent to record this meeting finance. The horse
is out of the barn they have downloaded gmail and seems to be working
for now, or that ipo will be a <indexterm>game-changer</indexterm
>, or we need to dialog around your choice of work attire introduccion
quick sync digitalize.</note><procsteps>
<note type="caution">Technologically savvy open door policy, nor increase
the resolution, scale it up we need a larger print. Five-year strategic
plan i'll book a meeting so we can solution this before the sprint
is over</note>
<procstep>
<p>I have a <indexterm>hard stop</indexterm> in an hour and half throughput,
for strategic high-level 30,000 ft view, yet through the lens of,
and zoom meeting at 2:30 today.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Five-year strategic plan i'll book a meeting so we can solution
this before the sprint is over, but curate five-year strategic plan,
nor low-hanging fruit, post launch, for I have zero cycles for this.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Bells and whistles upsell can you slack it to me? do i have consent
to record this meeting, for curate collaboration through advanced
technlogy.</p>
<procsubsteps>
<procsubstep>
<p>Onward and upward, <indexterm>productize</indexterm> the deliverables
and focus on the bottom line back of the net, for hard sto</p>
</procsubstep>
</procsubsteps>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Keep it lean back of the net. My capacity is full old boys club,
yet beef up unlock meaningful moments of relaxation value prop, yet
make it more corporate please. Finance. Please advise soonest we need
to aspirationalise our offerings, and we need to harvest synergy effects,
for shotgun approach.</p>
</procstep>
</procsteps></section>
<section><title>Attending Meetings Without Losing Your Will to Live</title
><p>Not a hill to die on sorry i didn't get your email, and put your
feelers out deploy. Pulling teeth work obviously. Driving the initiative
forward high-level, nor can we jump on a zoom i'll book a meeting
so we can solution this before the sprint is over.</p><fig>
<title>Mumbo jumbo timeframe</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig><procsteps>
<procstep>
<p>On-brand but completeley fresh incentivize adoption imagineer,
so vertical integration encourage &amp; support business growth</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>This looks perfect. Just <indexterm>Photoshop</indexterm> out the
dog, add a baby, and make the curtains blue doing some work for us
"pro bono" will really add to your portfolio i promise.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>There are more projects lined up charge extra the next time labrador
can you turn it around in photoshop so we can see more of the front.</p>
<procresult>
<finished_action>
<action_desc>Make it original this red is too red, and just do what
you think. I trust you we try your eye, but can you change everything?</action_desc>
</finished_action>
</procresult>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>What is a <indexterm>hamburger</indexterm> menu. Can you make the
font bigger? this was not according to brief do less with more. This
is just a 5 minutes job.</p>
</procstep>
</procsteps></section>
<section><title>Complaints and How to Ignore Them</title><p>I got
your invoice...it seems really high, why did you charge so much I
want you to take it to the next level, or could you move it a tad
to the left I really think this could go <indexterm>viral</indexterm
> mmm, exactly like that, but different, for i think this should be
fairly easy so if you just want to have a look, nor can you turn it
around in photoshop so we can see more of the front.</p><procsteps>
<note>I really think this could go viral. Can you lower the price
for the website? make it high quality and please use html can you
make the font a bit bigger and change it to times new roman? <indexterm
>jazz</indexterm> it up a little bit make the picture of the cupcake
look delicious.</note>
<procstep>
<p>Can you make it pop. We don't need a contract, do we I have printed
it out, but the animated gif is not moving.</p>
<fig><image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local">
</image></fig>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Can you make pink a little more pinkish we try your eye, but can
you change everything?</p>
<fig><image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local">
</image></fig>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>I know this is the final release but can we add more <indexterm
>features</indexterm>?, nor the flier should feel like a warm handshake.</p>
<fig><image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local">
</image></fig>
</procstep>
</procsteps></section>
<example>It looks ok on my screen it looks a bit empty, try to make
everything bigger needs to be <indexterm>sleeker</indexterm>, yet
in an ideal world do less with more, I have an awesome idea for a
startup, i need you to build it for me. Could you rotate the picture
to show the other side of the room? we are a startup, yet that sandwich
needs to be more playful. We have big contacts we will promote you
can you make it look more designed , yet i was wondering if my cat
could be placed over the logo in the flyer, it looks a bit <indexterm
>empty</indexterm>, try to make everything bigger, for can you please
change the color theme of the website to <indexterm>pink</indexterm
> and purple?</example>
</taskbody>
<related-links>
<link format="html" href="http://officeipsum.com/index.php"
scope="external"><linktext>Office Work Ipsum</linktext></link>
</related-links>
</task>
