<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2024, v.4002-->
<?Pub UDT instructions _comment?>
<?Pub UDT template _font?>
<?Pub Inc?>
<task id="TasksOfABoatswain-1E231301" rev="A.1" translate="yes"
xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd">
<title>Tasks of a Boatswain</title>
<shortdesc>Mutiny belaying pin draft lanyard ahoy spyglass rigging
reef hempen halter hardtack. Weigh anchor bilge rat bucko smartly
Cat o'nine tails scallywag fire ship rope's end coffer parrel. Tender
hardtack strike colors jury mast hands knave American Main Sink me
Barbary Coast squiffy. Clap of thunder wherry snow pink Plate Fleet
topmast grog cog boom loot. Piracy handsomely crow's nest mizzenmast
sutler jib chantey reef sails brigantine weigh anchor.</shortdesc>
<taskbody>
<prereq>Rum scallywag gangway maroon starboard Blimey yawl topsail
chandler belay. Sea Legs bilge water long boat reef sails lookout
draught bring a spring upon her cable Jolly Roger tack cutlass.<fig>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig></prereq>
<context>Hail-shot killick line driver aye spike. No prey, no pay
Brethren of the Coast belaying pin red ensign barkadeer deadlights.
Ballast spyglass barkadeer heave down prow tackle. Wench hands grapple
spanker maroon Cat o'nine tails. <indexterm>Lateen</indexterm> sail
barkadeer avast nipper Corsair cable. Cat o'nine tails heave to ho
wench boom Buccaneer. </context>
<steps>
<step><cmd>Scuppers holystone avast black spot loaded to the gunwalls
man-of-war. Jury <indexterm>mast rigging</indexterm> jack hands to
go on account code of conduct. </cmd></step>
<step><cmd>Six pounders lookout sheet <indexterm>interloper</indexterm
> piracy boatswain. Reef sails gibbet fore ahoy matey Davy Jones'
Locker. </cmd></step>
<step><cmd>American Main Jolly Roger list Blimey</cmd>
<stepresult><p>Brigantine rutters ahoy bilged on her anchor holystone
hulk. Topmast Jack Ketch long clothes Chain Shot pinnace hornswaggle.</p
></stepresult>
<steptroubleshooting><procsteps>
<procstep>
<p>Brigantine loot ahoy brig starboard aye.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Brigantine loot ahoy brig starboard aye.</p>
<note>Doubloon provost measured fer yer chains deadlights blow the
man down swab. Fore <indexterm>spanker</indexterm> Privateer six pounders
cable carouser.</note>
</procstep>
</procsteps></steptroubleshooting>
</step>
<step><cmd>American Main case shot lad chantey topgallant provost.
Long boat execution dock topmast<image
href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image></cmd>
</step>
<step><cmd>Transom mutiny ho main sheet Jack Ketch parley</cmd>
<substeps>
<substep><cmd>Nipper stern boatswain salmagundi jolly boat main sheet</cmd>
</substep>
<substep><cmd>Cable bilge snow spike Admiral of the <indexterm>Black
knave</indexterm></cmd></substep>
</substeps>
<choices>
<choice>Dead men tell no tales deadlights marooned yardarm take a
caulk long</choice>
<choice>Fire in the hole Letter of Marque measured fer yer chains
weigh anchor bounty jib.</choice>
</choices>
</step>
<step><cmd>Tackle reef Yellow Jack come about ho loot.</cmd>
<stepresult>Cable rope's end belay chantey tack Sea Legs. Arr heave
to boom snow Yellow Jack <indexterm>rum</indexterm>.</stepresult>
</step>
<step><cmd>Gangway topgallant ballast pink dance the hempen<indexterm
> jig port</indexterm>.</cmd></step>
</steps>
<result>Grog hornswaggle Pirate Round tender gangway main sheet. Run
a shot across the bow shrouds tackle broadside avast heave down. Run
a rig lanyard scuppers ballast trysail fathom. Long boat six pounders
fathom splice the main brace lee clipper. Rum lee wherry sloop boom
grog blossom. Long boat brigantine furl Letter of Marque booty list.
Rum lookout American Main brigantine Plate Fleet belay. Overhaul clipper
holystone take a caulk rigging rutters. <fig><image
href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image></fig
></result>
<example><fig><image href="10447755671.svg"
scope="local"></image></fig>Brigantine loot ahoy brig starboard aye.
Jack <indexterm>squiffy</indexterm> spyglass bilge Buccaneer mizzenmast.
Crack Jennys tea cup pirate walk the plank take a caulk mutiny spike.
Gaff ahoy ye starboard lugsail lad. Hulk keelhaul loot bilge ho swing
the lead. Doubloon provost measured fer yer chains deadlights blow
the man down swab. Fore spanker Privateer six pounders cable carouser.
American Main case shot lad chantey topgallant provost.</example>
</taskbody>
<related-links>
<link format="html" href="https://pirateipsum.me/#scrollstop"
scope="external"><linktext>Pirate Ipsum</linktext></link>
</related-links>
</task>
