<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2024, v.4002-->
<?Pub UDT instructions _comment?>
<?Pub Inc?>
<task id="NewNightlyNefariousKnightsOfTheNati-1E165300" rev="A.3"
translate="yes" xml:lang="en-US"
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd">
<title>New Nightly Nefarious Knights of the Nation</title>
<shortdesc>Unbowed, Unbent, Unbroken. Forgive my manners. I don't
see many ladies these days. Lucky for the ladies. Our Sun Shines Bright.
House Tarly of Horn Hill Can a man still be brave if he's afraid?</shortdesc>
<taskbody>
<context>When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. I
pledge my life and honor to the Night's Watch, for this night and
all the nights to come. The rains of castamere.</context>
<section><title>You Must Wear The Black Even If Its Not Your Color</title
><note type="danger">That is the only time a man can be brave. Unbowed,
Unbent, Unbroken. The <indexterm>Dothraki</indexterm> do things in
their own time, for their own reasons.</note><note type="warning"
>I would like a trial by combat. The battle of the <indexterm>redgrass</indexterm
> field. I would like a trial by combat. The War of the 5 kings.</note
><note>House Tarly of Horn Hill More pigeon pie, please. The bear
and the maiden fair. You know nothing, Jon Snow. The North remembers.
The winds of Winter. More pigeon pie, please. When you play the game
of thrones, you win or you die. I pledge my life and honor to the
Night's Watch, for this night and all the nights to come. The rains
of castamere. What is dead may never die.</note><procsteps>
<procstep>
<p></p>
<note>The night is dark and full of terrors. The bear and the maiden
fair.</note>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>The night is dark and full of terrors. The Dothraki do things in
their own time, for their own reasons.</p>
<note type="danger">King in the North</note>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>The tourney of Ashford Meadows. It is rare to meet a Lannister
who shares my enthusiasm for dead Lannisters. The rains of castamere.
The winds of Winter. King in the North. </p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. The rains
of castamere. A dream of Spring. The Dothraki do things in their own
time, for their own reasons.<indexterm> Dunc the Lunk</indexterm>,
thick as a castle wall.</p>
<note type="warning">Winter is coming</note>
<p>You know nothing, Jon Snow.</p>
<p>When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. The night
is dark and full of terrors. Never Resting. Fire and blood.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Bastards are born of passion, aren't they? We don't despise them
in <indexterm>Dorne</indexterm>. All men must die. Unbowed, Unbent,
Unbroken.</p>
<procresult>
<goto_action>
<action_desc>The Dothraki do things in their own time, for their own
reasons. What is dead may never die.</action_desc>
</goto_action>
</procresult>
</procstep>
</procsteps></section>
<section><title>Can A Man Still Be Brave If He's Afraid?</title><fig>
<title>It's Ten Thousand Miles Between Kings Landing And The Wall</title><?Pub
Caret -3?>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig><p>A good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act the good.
Each should have its own reward. As High as Honor. What is dead may
never die. As High as Honor. Words are like wind. Never Resting. A
good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act the good. Each should
have its own reward. May the Father judge him justly. Our Sun Shines
Bright. A forked purple lightning bolt, on black field speckled with
four-pointed stars. Dunc the Lunk, thick as a castle wall. The winds
of Winter.</p></section>
<context>A good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act the good.
Each should have its own reward. You know nothing, Jon Snow. A forked
purple lightning bolt, on black field speckled with four-pointed stars.
Forgive my manners. I don't see many ladies these days. Lucky for
the ladies.</context>
<steps>
<step><cmd>A Lannister always pays his debts. King in the North. It's
ten thousand miles between Kings landing and the wall. The wolf and
the lion.</cmd>
<choicetable>
<chhead>
<choptionhd>Option</choptionhd>
<chdeschd>Description</chdeschd></chhead>
<chrow>
<choption>A Lannister always pays his debts.</choption>
<chdesc>A Lannister always pays his debts.</chdesc></chrow>
</choicetable>
</step>
<step><cmd>A dream of Spring.<indexterm> King in the North</indexterm
>. As High as Honor. Can a man still be brave if he's afraid? That
is the only time a man can be brave.</cmd>
<substeps>
<substep><cmd>The bear and the maiden fair. The bear and the maiden
fair. Never Resting. It's ten thousand miles between Kings landing
and the wall.</cmd></substep>
<substep><cmd>You know nothing, <indexterm>Jon Snow</indexterm>. It's
ten thousand miles between Kings landing and the wall.</cmd>
<stepresult><p>Fire and blood. The winds of Winter. You know nothing,
Jon Snow. Dunc the Lunk, thick as a castle wall. The rains of castamere.
The War of the 5 kings. As High as Honor. You know nothing, Jon Snow.
Winter is coming. Unbowed, Unbent, Unbroken.</p></stepresult>
</substep>
<substep><cmd>A good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act
the good. Each should have its own reward. House <indexterm>Tarly</indexterm
> of Horn Hill King in the North.<image
href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image></cmd>
</substep>
</substeps>
</step>
<step><cmd>The tourney of Ashford Meadows. The Dothraki do things
in their own time, for their own reasons. Fire and blood. The War
of the 5 kings. And now his watch is ended.</cmd></step>
<step><cmd>King in the North. As High as Honor.<image
href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image></cmd>
</step>
<step><cmd>More <indexterm>pigeon</indexterm> pie, please. </cmd>
<stepresult><p>We don't despise them in Dorne. The battle of the redgrass
field. Winter is coming.</p></stepresult>
</step>
</steps>
<example>The battle of the redgrass field. The tourney of Ashford
Meadows. Unbowed, Unbent, Unbroken. The battle of the redgrass field.
All men must die. Never Resting. Dunc the Lunk, thick as a castle
wall. When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. The night
is dark and full of terrors. A good act does not wash out the bad,
nor a bad act the good. Each should have its own <indexterm>reward</indexterm
>.</example>
</taskbody>
<related-links>
<link format="html" href="https://game-of-thrones-ipsum.com/"
scope="external"><linktext>Game of Thrones Ipsum</linktext></link>
</related-links>
</task>
