<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2024, v.4002-->
<?Pub UDT instructions _comment?>
<?Pub UDT template _font?>
<?Pub Inc?>
<concept id="concept-1-43BF5456712" outputclass="intro2" rev="B.2"
translate="yes" xml:lang="en-US"
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd">
<title>Foreword</title>
<shortdesc>The Mobile Elevating Work Platform (MEWP) models covered
in this manual are designed and tested to meet or exceed various compliance
standards. Please refer to the manufacturer’s nameplate affixed to
the subject MEWP for specific standard compliance information.</shortdesc>
<conbody>
<p>This manual is a very important tool! Keep it with the machine
at all times.</p>
<p>The purpose of this manual is to provide owners, users, operators,
lessors, and lessees with the precautions and operating procedures
essential for the safe and proper machine operation for its intended
purpose.</p>
<p>Due to continuous product improvements, JLG Industries, Inc. reserves
the right to make specification changes without prior notification.
Contact JLG Industries, Inc. for updated information.</p>
<p>Refer to www.JLG.com for Warranty, Product Registration, and other
machine-related documentation.</p>
<section><title>Safety Alert Symbols And Safety Signal Words</title
><fig><image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local">
</image></fig><p>This is the Safety Alert Symbol. It is used to alert
you to the potential personal injury hazards. Obey all safety messages
that follow this symbol to avoid possible injury or death.</p><note
type="danger"><p>Indicates an imminently hazardous situation. If not
avoided, will result in serious injury or death. This decal will have
a red background.</p></note><note type="warning"><p>Indicates a potentially
hazardous situation. If not avoided, could result in serious injury
or death. This decal will have an orange background.</p></note><note
type="caution"><p>Indicates a potentially hazardous situation. If
not avoided, may result in minor or moderate injury. It may also alert
against unsafe practices. This decal will have a yellow background.</p
></note><note type="notice"><p>Indicates information or a company
policy that relates directly or indirectly to the safety of personnel
or protection of property.</p></note></section>
<section><title>Important Notices</title><note type="warning"><p>This
product must comply with all safety related bulletins. Contact JLG
Industries, Inc. or the local authorized JLG representative for information
regarding safety related bulletins which may have been issued for
this product.</p></note><note type="notice"><p>JLG Industries, Inc.
sends safety related bulletins to the owner of record of this machine.
Contact JLG Industries, Inc. to ensure that the current owner records
are updated and accurate.</p></note><note type="notice"><p>JLG Industries,
Inc. must be notified immediately in all instances where JLG products
have been involved in an accident involving bodily injury or death
or when substantial damage has occurred to personal property or the
JLG product.</p></note></section>
<section><title>Product Safety and Reliability</title><sectiondiv
><term>For:</term><ul>
<li><p>Accident Reporting</p></li>
<li><p>Product Safety Publications</p></li>
<li><p>Current Owner Updates</p></li>
<li><p>Questions Regarding Product Safety</p></li>
<li><p>Standards and Regulations Compliance Information</p></li>
<li><p>Questions Regarding Special Product Applications</p></li>
<li><p>Questions Regarding Product Modifications</p></li>
</ul></sectiondiv><sectiondiv><term>Contact:</term><p>Product Safety
and Reliability Department</p><p>JLG Industries, Inc.</p><p>13224
Fountainhead Plaza</p><p>Hagerstown, MD 21742</p><p>USA</p><p>or Visit
www.jlg.com to find your local JLG office.</p></sectiondiv><sectiondiv
><term>Contact:</term><p>Product Safety and Reliability Department</p
><p>JLG Industries, Inc.</p><p>13224 Fountainhead Plaza</p><p>Hagerstown,
MD 21742</p><p>USA</p><p>or Visit www.jlg.com to find your local JLG
office.</p></sectiondiv><sectiondiv><term>Contact:</term><p>Product
Safety and Reliability Department</p><p>JLG Industries, Inc.</p><p
>13224 Fountainhead Plaza</p><p>Hagerstown, MD 21742</p><p>USA</p
><p>or Visit www.jlg.com to find your local JLG office.</p></sectiondiv
><sectiondiv><term>In USA:</term><p>Toll Free: 877-JLG-SAFE (877-554-7233)</p
></sectiondiv><sectiondiv><term>Outside USA:</term><p>Phone: 240-420-2661</p
><p>Fax: 301-745-3713</p><p>E-mail: ProductSafety@JLG.com</p><?Pub _newline
?></sectiondiv></section><?Pub Caret -2?>
<section><title>Customer Feedback</title><p>JLG Industries values
the opinion of our customers and partners. We encourage you to provide
feedback on the quality and usability of this technical content by
emailing us at TechPubs@jlg.com.</p></section>
</conbody>
</concept>
