<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2021, v.4002--><?Pub UDT instructions _comment?><?Pub Inc?><task id="TasksToPleaseYourJavaOverlord-1E1CBBA0" rev="A.2" translate="yes" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd"><title>Tasks to Please Your Java Overlord</title><?Pub Caret -2?><shortdesc>Crema ut, cortado caffeine, con panna frappuccino, a doppio, sugar to go flavour, café au lait, blue mountain breve turkish coffee variety, french press and, doppio, coffee galão caramelization bar  latte cortado french press black frappuccino. Bar  at skinny, sugar, blue mountain est caffeine, a, blue mountain, aromatic flavour, french press cortado, pumpkin spice mazagran latte percolator coffee, sugar wings kopi-luwak strong, milk, dark id con panna frappuccino steamed rich kopi-luwak ut brewed barista grinder.</shortdesc><taskbody><prereq>Galão <indexterm>aroma</indexterm>, roast in, mazagran <indexterm>espresso</indexterm> id <indexterm>caffeine</indexterm> robusta saucer, brewed, aroma, bar , caramelization, roast, instant, whipped espresso cappuccino viennese white roast, latte qui so doppio mazagran crema instant. Cream, saucer organic robust et bar  to go milk robusta, at coffee flavour galão sugar <indexterm>trifecta</indexterm> to go single origin that café au lait crema,</prereq><steps><step><cmd>A affogato aromatic aroma java, at, extraction, cultivar, barista filter macchiato id, cream, dark, con panna, cup sit mocha body crema shop, grinder dark cappuccino, cinnamon whipped</cmd></step><step><cmd>Dripper, espresso brewed, variety iced aroma est grounds, to go, <indexterm>pumpkin spice</indexterm> <indexterm>organic</indexterm>, instant carajillo galão kopi-luwak dark robust seasonal sugar turkish con panna cup chicory saucer coffee, percolator lungo variety <indexterm>crema</indexterm> cinnamon</cmd><choices><choice>Single shot viennese flavour <indexterm>decaffeinated</indexterm> acerbic</choice><choice>Froth, whipped, cup, carajillo caramelization steamed milk </choice></choices></step><step><cmd>To go redeye, cup eu mazagran breve redeye robust steamed cream decaffeinated ut est, sweet flavour et, chicory instant espresso dripper café au lait. </cmd></step><step><cmd>Saucer irish arabica aged, cappuccino brewed, to go, viennese ristretto, flavour cortado, milk <indexterm>blue mountain</indexterm>, galão medium, wings froth half and half roast single shot, steamed black to go</cmd><stepresult><p>Half and half, et robust cultivar body, dark cortado, robust mazagran milk qui fair trade, wings as, medium, espresso sweet variety, at saucer caffeine cinnamon grinder americano, frappuccino qui, barista and foam extra  medium bar. </p></stepresult></step><step><cmd>Viennese aged cup iced, wings, irish mazagran dark single shot, cinnamon, and coffee carajillo aftertaste <indexterm>french press</indexterm> grinder arabica grounds arabica coffee mug skinny id at, barista milk in et cup irish. </cmd><substeps><substep><cmd>Cultivar a body coffee cultivar espresso medium, iced, latte</cmd></substep><substep><cmd>Aromatic, caramelization doppio milk, sit wings, aftertaste, in americano half and half trifecta</cmd></substep></substeps><choicetable><chhead><choptionhd>Option</choptionhd><chdeschd>Description</chdeschd></chhead><chrow><choption> Foam barista, coffee a, coffee, americano, barista</choption><chdesc>turkish cup chicory, skinny chicory, skinny galão rich brewed</chdesc></chrow></choicetable></step></steps><example>To go redeye, cup eu mazagran breve redeye robust steamed cream decaffeinated ut est, sweet flavour et, chicory instant espresso dripper café au lait. Medium, sugar <indexterm>half and half</indexterm> eu organic, cup, single shot, ut, instant saucer cup lungo, mazagran variety seasonal body est black siphon. Filter single origin lungo aromatic whipped macchiato iced, cortado viennese strong, aroma turkish, sweet americano grounds, turkish white froth robust, breve cinnamon medium, acerbic extra  galão café au lait seasonal coffee bar  instant. Doppio, qui whipped in brewed, cappuccino decaffeinated chicory extraction foam irish sweet variety acerbic <indexterm>irish</indexterm> extraction, medium con panna, aroma turkish cream organic to go. Medium chicory blue mountain, to go doppio medium, milk white con panna id macchiato froth organic dripper aromatic crema, mug flavour, carajillo, est fair trade saucer carajillo mocha lungo strong. Mocha, beans, single origin java, extra  froth turkish, cup, crema shop americano aged robust coffee, bar  frappuccino french press siphon milk, cup, chicory fair trade mocha, lungo, fair trade doppio cappuccino, robust single origin <indexterm>redeye</indexterm> variety rich decaffeinated.</example></taskbody><related-links><link format="html" href="https://baconipsum.com/" scope="external"><linktext>Bacon Ipsum</linktext></link><linklist><link format="html" href="http://coffeeipsum.com/" scope="external"><linktext>Coffee Ipsum</linktext></link></linklist></related-links></task>