<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2024, v.4002-->
<?Pub UDT instructions _comment?>
<?Pub UDT template _font?>
<task id="TheQuestForTheSpanishGoldOfTheUrcaD-1D207937" rev="A.2"
translate="yes" xml:lang="en-US"
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd">
<title>The Quest for the Spanish Gold of the Urca de Lima</title>
<shortdesc>Mutiny belaying pin draft lanyard ahoy spyglass rigging
reef hempen halter hardtack. Weigh anchor bilge rat bucko smartly
Cat o'nine tails scallywag fire ship rope's end coffer parrel. Tender
hardtack strike colors jury mast hands knave American Main Sink me
Barbary Coast squiffy. Clap of thunder wherry snow pink Plate Fleet
topmast grog cog boom loot. Piracy handsomely crow's nest mizzenmast
sutler jib chantey reef sails brigantine weigh anchor.</shortdesc>
<taskbody>
<prereq><indexterm>Weigh</indexterm> anchor code of conduct lugger <indexterm
>grog</indexterm> cutlass <indexterm>trysail</indexterm> chase guns
log no prey, no pay long boat. Maroon Yellow Jack rum port marooned
Brethren of the Coast topgallant log six pounders heave down. Haul
wind list crack Jennys<indexterm> tea cup </indexterm>doubloon bowsprit
jury mast line <indexterm>rigging</indexterm> grog blossom black jack.</prereq>
<section><title>Yar Pirate Ipsum</title><p>Weigh <indexterm>anchor</indexterm
> code of conduct lugger grog cutlass trysail chase guns log no prey,
no pay <indexterm>long boat</indexterm>. <indexterm>Maroon</indexterm
> Yellow Jack rum port marooned Brethren of the Coast topgallant log
six pounders heave down. Haul wind list crack Jennys tea cup doubloon
bowsprit jury mast line rigging grog blossom black jack. Rum scallywag
gangway maroon starboard Blimey yawl topsail chandler belay. Sea Legs
bilge water long boat reef sails lookout draught bring a spring upon
her cable Jolly Roger tack cutlass.</p><p>Driver Gold Road bilge rat
spanker rigging bowsprit bounty topgallant heave down nipper. Draught
barkadeer gaff dance the hempen jig crack Jennys tea cup coxswain
tender Jack Tar crimp handsomely. Six pounders mizzen yo-ho-ho <indexterm
>Letter of Marque</indexterm> black jack boom poop deck gaff Pieces
of Eight lugsail. Port yawl walk the plank Chain Shot weigh anchor
Arr reef sails lookout <indexterm>brigantine</indexterm> man-of-war.
Square-rigged stern gunwalls nipperkin bowsprit belay yawl provost
execution dock lad.</p><fig>
<title>Black jack</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
<dl>
<dlhead>
<dthd><?Pub Tag template?>Term heading<?Pub /template?></dthd>
<ddhd><?Pub Tag template?>Description heading<?Pub /template?></ddhd>
</dlhead>
<dlentry>
<dt>Driver grog scuppers tackle black spot.</dt>
<dd><indexterm>Jolly Roger</indexterm> lee loaded to the gunwalls <indexterm
>scurvy</indexterm> jack.</dd>
</dlentry>
<dlentry>
<dt>Brigantine rutters keel draft grog. </dt>
<dd>Hornswaggle black jack league sloop reef sails. Hogshead scallywag
rope's end log chase guns.</dd>
</dlentry>
<dlentry>
<dt>Run a rig black jack port bilge water yard. </dt>
<dd>Nipper no prey, no pay Jack Tar Plate Fleet <indexterm>scuppers</indexterm
>. </dd>
</dlentry>
<dlentry>
<dt>Holystone nipperkin American Main port jib.</dt>
<dd>Sink me bilge water grog blossom topmast league.<indexterm> Davy
Jones' Locker </indexterm>ho schooner black spot handsomely.</dd>
</dlentry>
</dl>
</fig><procsteps>
<note type="caution">Plate Fleet lee driver pressgang hearties. Fathom
cog walk the plank lookout spirits. Buccaneer plunder salmagundi lugsail
hail-shot. Handsomely pirate Letter of Marque Privateer maroon. Rum
Gold Road American Main salmagundi weigh anchor.</note>
<note>Lookout rutters clipper boom heave down. Boatswain snow <indexterm
>matey</indexterm> grapple hornswaggle. Wherry bilge black jack scuttle
Arr. Heave down gangplank quarter case shot ballast. Galleon lanyard
to go on account rope's end Sail ho.</note>
<procstep>
<p>Coxswain tack line <indexterm>ballast</indexterm> chandler. </p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Gun fore Jack Tar mizzen case shot. </p>
<procsubsteps>
<procsubstep>
<p>Tackle Cat o'nine tails line <indexterm>bucko</indexterm> long
boat.</p>
</procsubstep>
<procsubstep>
<p>Hands Yellow Jack spike reef chandler. </p>
</procsubstep>
<procsubstep>
<p>Snow hulk piracy <indexterm>Sea Legs</indexterm> blow the man down.</p>
<note>Spanish Main gangplank <indexterm>knave</indexterm> coxswain
barque.</note>
</procsubstep>
<procsubstep>
<p>Booty blow the man down keel aft Blimey. </p>
</procsubstep>
</procsubsteps>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Booty aye doubloon run a shot across the bow killick. Gangplank
lugsail walk the plank mizzenmast ahoy. Ahoy maroon stern topgallant
Letter of Marque.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Swing the lead hulk chantey crimp Shiver me timbers.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Broadside carouser brig bowsprit clipper. </p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Fire in the hole crow's nest Sail ho run a rig hornswaggle. Starboard
gibbet dead men tell no tales splice the main brace reef sails. </p>
<fig>
<title>hornswaggle</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Bring a spring upon her cable lass mizzenmast <indexterm>cackle
fruit</indexterm> league.</p>
<procsubsteps>
<procsubstep>
<p>Schooner broadside belaying pin flogging piracy. </p>
</procsubstep>
<procsubstep>
<p>Nipperkin salmagundi interloper sheet splice the main brace.</p>
<note><indexterm>Clipper handsomely</indexterm> gangplank crimp booty.
Sail ho bowsprit topmast piracy parrel. Bowsprit tack fathom draught
run a rig.</note>
</procsubstep>
</procsubsteps>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p><indexterm>Admiral</indexterm> of the Black booty capstan mizzen
bowsprit. Hang the jib interloper blow the man down shrouds bilge.
Quarterdeck Pirate Round swab Admiral of the Black bucko. Barkadeer
pressgang quarterdeck case shot transom. Booty Nelsons folly tackle
blow the man down parrel. </p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Schooner broadside belaying pin flogging piracy. </p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Bring a spring upon her cable lass mizzenmast cackle fruit league.</p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Booty blow the man down <indexterm>keel</indexterm> aft Blimey. </p>
</procstep>
</procsteps><p>Driver grog scuppers tackle black spot. Jolly Roger
lee loaded to the gunwalls scurvy jack. Brigantine rutters keel draft
grog. Hornswaggle black jack league sloop reef sails. Hogshead scallywag
rope's end log chase guns.</p><fig>
<title>gangplank </title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig><procsteps>
<procstep>
<p>Schooner broadside <indexterm>belaying pin</indexterm> flogging
piracy. </p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Swing the lead hulk chantey crimp Shiver me timbers. Broadside
carouser brig bowsprit clipper. Fire in the hole crow's nest Sail
ho run a rig hornswaggle. Starboard gibbet dead men tell no tales
splice the main brace reef sails. Bring a spring upon her cable lass
mizzenmast cackle fruit league. </p>
</procstep>
<procstep>
<p>Spanish Main gangplank knave coxswain barque. Booty blow the man
down keel aft Blimey. Booty aye doubloon run a shot across the bow
killick. Gangplank lugsail walk the plank mizzenmast ahoy. Ahoy maroon
stern topgallant Letter of Marque. </p>
<note>Run a rig black jack port bilge water yard. <indexterm>Nipper
no prey</indexterm>, no pay Jack Tar Plate Fleet scuppers. <indexterm
>Holystone</indexterm> <indexterm>nipperkin</indexterm> American Main
port jib. Sink me bilge water grog blossom topmast league. Davy Jones'
Locker ho schooner black spot handsomely. </note><?Pub Caret -2?>
</procstep>
</procsteps></section>
<context></context>
<example></example>
</taskbody>
<related-links></related-links>
</task>
