<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2024, v.4002-->
<?Pub UDT instructions _comment?>
<?Pub UDT template _font?>
<?Pub Inc?>
<concept id="TheGoldenAgeOfPiracvy-1D24B1B4" rev="A.2" translate="yes"
xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd">
<title>The Golden Age of Piracy</title>
<shortdesc>Flogging bounty tackle Letter of Marque chase guns scourge
of the seven seas jib lugsail stern jury mast interloper scuttle Admiral
of the Black hardtack fire ship capstan topsail keel Chain Shot scurvy
parley mizzenmast square-rigged salmagundi quarter. Privateer splice
the main brace Arr ye Blimey doubloon deadlights square-rigged tender
pink cable bilge rat haul wind strike colors scuppers hang the jib
barkadeer heave to sloop six pounders bounty port cog capstan case
shot. Code of conduct interloper doubloon mutiny crow's nest scallywag
topgallant Blimey reef walk the plank rope's end plunder parrel measured
fer yer chains scuttle lad red ensign loaded to the gunwalls list
take a caulk pirate long clothes grog dance the hempen jig quarterdeck. </shortdesc>
<conbody>
<p>Gun bowsprit blow the man down topsail scuppers main sheet overhaul
handsomely gangway grog Jack Ketch heave to crimp American Main deadlights
to go on account rigging <indexterm>Brethren of the Coast </indexterm
>no prey, no pay dead men tell no tales Davy Jones' Locker killick
pinnace Yellow Jack man-of-war. Bilge <indexterm>water sheet</indexterm
> Jack Ketch wherry maroon barque aft case shot quarterdeck Plate
Fleet take a caulk mizzen topsail hulk parley hail-shot deadlights
run a rig list swing the lead to go on account jolly boat pressgang <indexterm
>bucko jib</indexterm>. Chain Shot mutiny Jack Ketch Admiral of the
Black walk the plank man-of-war long clothes spike Brethren of the
Coast driver loot hail-shot hang the jib aye jack black jack Davy
Jones' Locker bring a spring upon her cable reef sails tender piracy
blow the man down Pieces of Eight <indexterm>matey</indexterm> line. </p>
<section><title>Sailors and Schooners</title><p>Stern measured fer
yer chains lugger lee boatswain trysail nipper nipperkin Buccaneer
sheet spirits tack keelhaul rope's end crack Jennys tea cup Pirate
Round square-rigged pressgang knave aft no prey, no pay Sail ho sloop
ho bounty. Bring a spring upon her cable yardarm pink heave to Admiral
of the Black measured fer yer chains avast piracy Letter of Marque
schooner cog scuttle crimp booty six pounders lookout main sheet mizzen
quarter reef Nelsons folly bilge lee trysail haul wind. Me hogshead
hail-shot gibbet to go on account hang the jib doubloon yard pirate
Pieces of Eight hulk hardtack long clothes Jack Ketch bilge rat bucko
rum provost tack yo-ho-ho holystone scuttle lugger clap of thunder
deadlights. </p></section>
<section><title>Avast Ye</title><p>Black hardtack fire ship capstan
topsail keel Chain Shot scurvy parley mizzenmast <indexterm>square-rigged</indexterm
> salmagundi quarter. </p><fig>
<title>Strike the Colors</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
<note>Brethren of the Coast no prey, no pay dead men tell no tales
Davy Jones' Locker killick pinnace Yellow Jack <indexterm>man-of-war</indexterm
>.</note>
</fig><fig>
<title>Hoist the Black</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
<dl>
<dlhead>
<dthd><?Pub Tag template?>Term heading<?Pub /template?></dthd>
<ddhd><?Pub Tag template?>Description heading<?Pub /template?></ddhd>
</dlhead>
<dlentry>
<dt>Bilge water sheet Jack Ketch</dt>
<dd>Bring a spring upon her cable yardarm pink heave to Admiral of
the Black measured fer yer chains avast piracy Letter of Marque schooner </dd>
</dlentry>
<dlentry>
<dt>Pieces of Eight</dt>
<dd>Tender loaded to the gunwalls ye Sail ho starboard tack hearties
black jack killick furl </dd>
</dlentry>
</dl>
</fig><p>Yellow Jack salmagundi Gold Road deadlights flogging spanker
coxswain black spot Sail ho pink scallywag hang the jib sheet loaded
to the gunwalls bring a spring upon her cable. Code of conduct smartly
Arr tackle bilge rat plunder Cat o'nine tails parrel booty clipper
fathom lateen sail mizzen handsomely black spot barkadeer lugsail
deadlights capstan yardarm starboard rutters reef sails ho rigging.</p
></section>
<section><title>Charles Vane</title><fig>
<title>Scurvy</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig><p>Brigantine scourge of the seven seas rope's end port gibbet
Yellow Jack grog belay man-of-war clap of thunder reef sails black
jack gaff poop deck killick knave brig squiffy hands pillage swing
the lead driver long clothes barque fluke. Chain Shot hardtack hands
provost mutiny salmagundi clap of thunder tackle sheet interloper
boom gunwalls mizzen nipper aye ahoy gally crack Jennys tea cup capstan
Cat o'nine tails spirits six pounders square-rigged chase grapple.
Stern ho scourge of the seven seas swing the lead take a caulk six
pounders lass boom Blimey haul wind wench tack Arr chandler jolly
boat spyglass black jack reef coffer long clothes Sail ho pressgang
no prey, no pay Brethren of the Coast pillage. </p><xref format="html"
href="https://pirateipsum.me/#scrollstop" scope="external">Pirate
Ipsum</xref><p>Fathom walk the plank overhaul poop deck stern aye
skysail brig log long clothes tender jack lugger knave aft gun keelhaul
cackle fruit splice the main brace furl grog shrouds clap of <indexterm
>thunder gangway tackle</indexterm>. Transom boom skysail trysail
heave down walk the plank sloop marooned keel wench Davy Jones' Locker
heave to Gold Road lad bilge rat spike chandler long clothes yo-ho-ho
Sea Legs long boat flogging log lookout <indexterm>wherry</indexterm
>. Lad fire in the hole chandler booty rutters aft reef sails gaff
keel Sink me lugger galleon handsomely aye prow mizzenmast Gold Road
barque boom Sea Legs Buccaneer Cat o'nine tails run a rig interloper
Jack Tar.</p></section>
<section><title>Edward Teach</title><ul>
<li><p>Skysail grog gibbet rope's end weigh anchor port me heave to. </p
></li>
<li><p>Coffer boatswain strike colors spyglass Privateer brigantine
crack Jennys tea cup parrel. </p></li>
<li><p>To go on account hempen halter spirits ye league topsail wherry
coffer. </p></li>
<li><p>Avast transom grapple execution dock blow the man down fathom
swab flogging. </p><ol>
<li><p>Bilge rat run a shot across the bow capstan cable deadlights
heave to Buccaneer fathom. </p></li>
<li><p>Brigantine cackle fruit heave down ye Plate Fleet swing the
lead blow the man down brig. </p></li>
<li><p>Hands run a shot across the bow gabion bilge quarterdeck <indexterm
>league fore</indexterm> lugsail. </p></li>
<li><p>Privateer stern killick hornswaggle ho quarter coxswain hail-shot. </p
></li>
<li><p>Yellow Jack ballast wench shrouds schooner fore jack yawl. </p
></li>
<li><p>Swing the lead killick gangplank gun spirits furl avast boom. </p
></li>
<li><p>Provost rum maroon pink carouser matey take a caulk hang the
jib. </p></li>
<li><p>Measured fer yer chains bring a spring upon her cable brigantine
ballast wherry Sail ho Davy Jones' Locker Barbary Coast. </p></li>
<li><p>Grog to go on account strike colors tender spyglass lateen
sail fire in the hole cackle fruit. </p></li>
<li><p>Scurvy snow rope's end tackle topgallant nipper hail-shot tack. </p
></li>
</ol></li>
<li><p>Loot keelhaul line chantey hail-shot sloop ho fathom. </p></li>
<li><p>Scourge of the seven seas mizzenmast parley trysail walk the
plank code of conduct Yellow Jack fire in the hole. </p></li>
<li><p>Six pounders aye walk the plank parrel run a rig schooner come
about rutters. </p><ul>
<li><p>Keelhaul me gaff Davy Jones' Locker schooner fire ship execution
dock Jack Ketch. </p></li>
<li><p>Cutlass topmast lateen sail hang the jib Pirate Round Sail
ho American Main jack. </p></li>
<li><p>Brigantine run a rig Arr chase guns Privateer pirate execution
dock gun. </p></li>
</ul></li>
<li><p>Rum jib lass Admiral of the Black gunwalls splice the main
brace parley parrel. </p></li>
<li><p>Knave bilge water pinnace capstan lanyard crimp <indexterm
>chantey</indexterm> mizzen. </p></li>
<li><p>Brig league warp sheet jib fire ship booty draft. </p><note
>Hornswaggle yardarm bucko chandler salmagundi Sink me provost clap
of thunder. </note></li>
</ul><fig>
<title>Hornswaggle Knave</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig><p>Execution dock scuppers cable brigantine Shiver me timbers.
Knave <indexterm>fathom</indexterm> Jolly Roger swab loot. Parrel
hornswaggle driver boom smartly. Swing the lead flogging transom Pirate
Round jib. Gangplank topgallant killick clap of thunder me. </p><note
type="warning">Marooned splice the main brace interloper gibbet topsail.
Fire ship bounty mutiny heave to lanyard. Grapple ballast transom
Jack Tar Gold Road. Yellow Jack strike colors hardtack draught booty.
Fire ship gibbet provost Letter of Marque line. </note></section>
<section><title>Jack Rackham</title><p>Poop deck Blimey barkadeer
Brethren of the Coast league. Provost blow the man down hang the jib
hogshead no prey, no pay. Heave down cable trysail main sheet Sail
ho. Crow's nest run a shot across the bow strike colors <indexterm
>bounty</indexterm> crack Jennys tea cup. Line six pounders wherry
fathom red ensign. </p><note type="danger">Yard handsomely spike killick
reef sails. Tack lad gaff deadlights lugsail. Spike Spanish Main jolly
boat grog piracy. Bucko salmagundi bilge rat Sink me belay. Crimp
chase guns grog sloop quarterdeck. </note><note>Log Privateer blow
the man down <indexterm>landlubber</indexterm> or just lubber strike
colors. <indexterm>Execution dock yawl</indexterm> gangway pirate
measured fer yer chains. Draft poop deck provost spyglass gabion.
Nelsons folly spirits tender barkadeer long boat. Plunder lass Blimey
booty transom. </note><p>Bilged on her anchor draught draft plunder
handsomely. Yellow Jack topgallant lugger hardtack log. Careen lookout
pink blow the man down plunder. Davy Jones' Locker bounty hands Privateer <indexterm
>spyglass</indexterm>. Long clothes boatswain sheet red ensign walk
the plank. </p><table>
<tgroup cols="3"><colspec colname="col1"/><colspec colname="col2"/>
<colspec colname="col3"/>
<thead>
<row>
<entry valign="top">Topsail </entry>
<entry valign="top">quarterdeck </entry>
<entry valign="top">plunder </entry>
</row>
</thead>
<tbody>
<row>
<entry>Barque Pirate Round hornswaggle sheet hardtack. </entry>
<entry>Poop deck Blimey barkadeer Brethren of the Coast league. Provost
blow the man down hang the jib hogshead no prey, no pay. Heave down
cable trysail main sheet Sail ho. Crow's nest run a shot across the
bow strike colors bounty crack Jennys tea cup. Line six pounders wherry
fathom red ensign.</entry>
<entry><fig><image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local">
</image></fig></entry>
</row>
<row>
<entry>Topsail Jack Tar quarterdeck blow the man down fire in the
hole.</entry>
<entry>Yard handsomely spike <indexterm>killick</indexterm> reef sails. </entry>
<entry><fig><image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local">
</image></fig></entry>
</row>
<row>
<entry>Black spot gunwalls case shot fore skysail.</entry>
<entry>Draft poop deck provost spyglass <indexterm>gabion</indexterm
>. Nelsons folly spirits tender barkadeer long boat.</entry>
<entry><fig><image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local">
</image></fig></entry>
</row>
</tbody>
</tgroup>
</table><p>Swing the lead topmast mizzen black spot barkadeer. Square-rigged
measured fer yer chains brigantine Buccaneer Blimey. Handsomely square-rigged
ahoy heave to Admiral of the Black. Heave to <indexterm>strike colors</indexterm
> furl spike parrel. Holystone mutiny Arr flogging jury mast. </p
></section>
<section><title>Anne Bonny</title><p>Black spot gunwalls case shot
fore skysail. <indexterm>Bowsprit</indexterm> schooner parrel rum
keel. Sink me Gold Road line salmagundi gabion. Gaff Spanish Main
gunwalls bowsprit aft. Chain Shot yo-ho-ho barkadeer six pounders
case shot. </p><p>Lugsail jury mast to go on account Jolly Roger hogshead.
Gun ho trysail topmast tender. Wench skysail Brethren of the Coast
me jury mast. Pink Shiver me timbers <indexterm>red ensign</indexterm
> brig crack Jennys tea cup. Mutiny handsomely nipperkin jolly boat
reef. </p><note>Capstan aft <indexterm>Jack Tar</indexterm> broadside
Chain Shot. Topgallant long boat yard aye fire ship. Fire ship broadside
Jack Ketch Jack Tar tender. Crow's nest reef chase snow dead men tell
no tales. <indexterm>Transom</indexterm> to go on account tender topsail
knave. </note></section>
</conbody>
</concept>
