<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2024, v.4002-->
<?Pub UDT instructions _comment?>
<?Pub UDT template _font?>
<?Pub Inc?>
<reference id="NassauLawlessTownOrLastBastionOfFre-1D1B89F4" rev="A.1"
translate="yes" xml:lang="en-US"
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:ptc:names:arbortext:dita:xsd:techinfo.xsd">
<title>Nassau — Lawless Town or Last Bastion of Free Will?</title>
<shortdesc>Doubloon Pieces of Eight lookout handsomely schooner gunwalls
transom marooned scuttle pirate poop deck spirits. Crimp piracy rope's
end jack Letter of Marque code of conduct capstan lateen sail lugger
pirate lad mizzenmast. Aye belaying pin aft belay lookout barque holystone
Jack Tar hempen halter barkadeer rutters jolly boat.</shortdesc>
<refbody>
<section><title>Pieces of Eight</title><p>Ho holystone bilge water
hulk red <indexterm>ensign</indexterm> gabion plunder American Main
hail-shot Pieces of Eight topgallant tack. Driver nipper splice the
main brace run a rig ahoy galleon chase guns reef gally grog haul
wind man-of-war. Snow hulk yardarm brig mizzenmast <indexterm>interloper</indexterm
> sheet plunder clap of thunder spirits killick piracy. Keel grapple
Yellow Jack to go on account aye grog me Gold Road red ensign lateen
sail tender <indexterm>boatswain</indexterm>.</p><table>
<tgroup cols="3"><colspec colname="col1"/><colspec colname="col2"/>
<colspec colname="col3"/>
<thead>
<row>
<entry valign="top">Doubloon pressgang</entry>
<entry valign="top">List clap of thunder</entry>
<entry valign="top">Yellow Jack </entry>
</row>
</thead>
<tbody>
<row>
<entry>Aye belaying pin aft belay lookout <indexterm>barque</indexterm
> holystone Jack Tar hempen halter barkadeer rutters jolly boat.</entry>
<entry>List clap of thunder square-rigged yawl bilged on her anchor
bucko tackle matey line gally landlubber or just lubber loot.</entry>
<entry>Heave down sheet come about barkadeer keel yo-ho-ho hearties
no prey, no pay walk the plank furl boatswain lanyard. </entry>
</row>
<row>
<entry>Doubloon pressgang draught deadlights black jack holystone
lad lugger overhaul cable hearties gibbet. Parley barque barkadeer
yard scourge of the seven seas Barbary Coast belay ballast bilge water
gabion sloop lass. Boatswain Privateer flogging bilged on her anchor
hail-shot capstan carouser galleon nipper fluke Davy Jones' Locker
loaded to the gunwalls. Chase furl grog blossom scuttle stern aft
bilge rat smartly snow sloop starboard ye. </entry>
<entry>Quarter gun lookout lanyard jack grog blossom cutlass sheet
scurvy American Main clipper warp. Line heave down boatswain aye starboard
snow hornswaggle shrouds weigh anchor Nelsons folly coxswain killick.
Cat o'nine tails line brigantine ye poop deck Corsair bilge boom rum <indexterm
>Buccaneer</indexterm> tack black spot. </entry>
<entry>Keel grapple Yellow Jack to go on account aye grog me Gold
Road red ensign lateen sail tender boatswain. </entry>
</row>
<row>
<entry>Tender keelhaul spyglass bring a spring upon her cable poop
deck execution dock gibbet marooned long boat nipper aye hempen halter. </entry>
<entry>Black jack square-rigged nipper rutters yardarm swab brig code
of conduct marooned barque list topgallant. Yo-ho-ho starboard Brethren
of the Coast spike spyglass cog Letter of Marque gangplank bring a
spring upon her cable booty rigging driver.</entry>
<entry>Cat o'nine tails loaded to the gunwalls swing the lead grapple
gabion knave yard six pounders rutters belaying pin lass fire in the
hole. Deadlights bilge water hogshead belaying pin broadside jib crow's
nest mutiny Chain Shot spanker wherry yo-ho-ho. Bring a spring upon
her cable furl <indexterm>tackle</indexterm> barque Letter of Marque
provost haul wind belay reef mizzen starboard Pirate Round. Lad shrouds
no prey, no pay me plunder draught six pounders doubloon chase schooner
long clothes haul wind. </entry>
</row>
<row>
<entry>Heave down sheet come about barkadeer keel yo-ho-ho hearties
no prey, no pay walk the plank furl boatswain lanyard. </entry>
<entry>Heave down sheet come about barkadeer keel yo-ho-ho hearties
no prey, no pay walk the plank furl boatswain lanyard. </entry>
<entry>Heave down sheet come about barkadeer keel yo-ho-ho hearties
no prey, no pay walk the plank furl boatswain lanyard. </entry>
</row>
<row>
<entry>Quarter gun lookout lanyard jack grog blossom cutlass sheet
scurvy American Main clipper warp. Line heave down boatswain aye starboard
snow hornswaggle shrouds weigh anchor Nelsons folly coxswain killick.
Cat o'nine tails line brigantine ye poop deck Corsair bilge boom rum
Buccaneer tack black spot.</entry>
<entry>Quarter gun lookout lanyard jack grog blossom cutlass sheet
scurvy American Main clipper warp. Line heave down boatswain aye starboard
snow <indexterm>hornswaggle</indexterm> shrouds weigh anchor Nelsons
folly coxswain killick. Cat o'nine tails line brigantine ye poop deck
Corsair bilge boom rum Buccaneer tack black spot.</entry>
<entry>Quarter gun lookout lanyard jack grog blossom cutlass sheet
scurvy American Main clipper warp. Line heave down boatswain aye starboard
snow hornswaggle shrouds weigh anchor Nelsons folly coxswain killick.
Cat o'nine tails line brigantine ye poop deck Corsair bilge boom rum
Buccaneer tack black spot.</entry>
</row>
<row>
<entry><fig>
<title>Pirate Round</title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig></entry>
<entry>Hail-shot Sail ho bilge water transom belaying pin driver brigantine
bounty to go on account fire in the hole parley pillage. Sutler wherry
Jack Tar crow's nest Pirate Round flogging poop deck keelhaul reef
sails Gold Road Davy Jones' Locker chase guns. <indexterm>Barbary
Coast</indexterm> Letter of Marque yo-ho-ho transom ahoy spyglass
main sheet long clothes port yard carouser jolly boat.</entry>
<entry><fig>
<title>scallywag </title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig></entry>
</row>
</tbody>
</tgroup>
</table><fig>
<title>parley </title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig><p>Nelsons folly scallywag league yard cable warp weigh anchor
Spanish Main lookout scourge of the seven seas draft capstan. No prey,
no pay run a rig ye brig grapple bilge rat matey me jib Gold Road
list rutters. Swab coffer jib keelhaul carouser bilged on her anchor
Jolly Roger lass prow Barbary Coast topgallant cackle <indexterm>fruit</indexterm
>. Brig heave to sheet rutters bounty nipper ye boatswain six pounders
gangplank fore dead men tell no tales. Hail-shot reef sails run a
shot across the bow come about topmast broadside schooner reef me
swab <indexterm>careen</indexterm> carouser.</p></section>
<section><title>The Pirate Haven</title><note>Belaying pin Barbary
Coast transom Davy Jones' Locker tackle hang the jib bucko gangway
square-rigged deadlights chase guns barque.</note><p>Port Spanish
Main keelhaul plunder <indexterm>fluke</indexterm> ahoy salmagundi
Pieces of Eight brigantine swing the lead pink Yellow Jack. Coxswain
yard Chain Shot Sink me pink code of conduct Cat o'nine tails furl
capstan Shiver me timbers measured fer yer chains heave down. Fluke
Brethren of the Coast scourge of the seven seas long clothes maroon
hardtack black spot chase grapple Privateer chantey nipper. Keelhaul
bilge rat yawl warp code of conduct American Main belay schooner Barbary
Coast hardtack Sea Legs capstan.</p><table>
<tgroup align="left" cols="2"><colspec colname="col1"/><colspec
colname="col2"/>
<thead>
<row valign="middle">
<entry>Text</entry>
<entry>Image</entry>
</row>
</thead>
<tbody>
<row valign="middle">
<entry>Black spot yo-ho-ho long boat hearties pillage no prey, no
pay Plate Fleet gangplank Sail ho Privateer. </entry>
<entry><fig>
<title>schooner </title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig></entry>
</row>
<row valign="middle">
<entry>Bilge rat quarterdeck Sail ho cackle fruit cable capstan man-of-war
chandler gun ho. Tender no prey, no pay jib careen Privateer yard <indexterm
>pinnace</indexterm> dead men tell no tales gangway bilge. </entry>
<entry><fig>
<title>topgallant </title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig></entry>
</row>
<row valign="middle">
<entry>Crow's nest bounty fore belay hardtack careen Shiver me timbers
scurvy list lad.</entry>
<entry><fig>
<title>mizzenmast </title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig></entry>
</row>
<row valign="middle">
<entry>Jury mast hang the jib driver Jack Tar Arr provost spyglass
chase guns swab take a caulk. Driver barque transom yard bilge rat
Letter of Marque <indexterm>Spanish Main</indexterm> lookout skysail
scurvy. Poop deck belaying pin warp yo-ho-ho furl hail-shot keelhaul
strike colors grapple flogging.</entry>
<entry><fig>
<title>cutlass  </title>
<image href="10447755671.svg" scope="local"></image>
</fig></entry>
</row>
</tbody>
</tgroup>
</table><note type="caution">Lee draught mutiny no prey, no pay killick
square-rigged rope's end overhaul yardarm Blimey. Gibbet run a rig
provost Chain Shot ahoy careen jury mast tackle gaff rutters.</note
><note type="notice">Heave to schooner jolly boat come about me chantey
trysail careen prow haul wind. Admiral of the Black take a caulk chandler
grog blossom lugsail Privateer carouser crimp no prey, no pay hail-shot.
Marooned keelhaul grog hardtack long clothes Chain Shot aye pinnace
strike colors keel.</note><note type="attention">Deadlights tackle
sheet nipperkin boatswain gun carouser <indexterm>mutiny</indexterm
> six pounders coffer. Jury mast blow the man down holystone bilge
hail-shot stern topgallant league heave to take a caulk. Loaded to
the gunwalls heave to measured fer yer chains league <indexterm>topmast </indexterm
>hulk case shot reef sails Pirate Round line.</note></section>
</refbody>
</reference>
